Ahereza Juliet

Software Developer

Tel: 0776380488 / 0756513199 Email: <u>aherezajuliet8@gmail.com</u>

GitHub:

https://github.com/AJuliet8/mydaystardaycare2024.git

https://github.com/AJuliet8/consmetics-products.git still working on it

About Me

With a background in social work and a passion for coding, I bring a unique blend of empathy and technical expertise to the table. I excel in roles where I can leverage my coding skills to interact with customers, understand their needs, and deliver effective programming solutions. My proficiency spans across backend development, with a readiness to adapt to frontend and other software development aspects as required.

Skills

- **Programming Languages:** JavaScript
- Frameworks and Technologies: Angular JS, Bootstrap, Vue. js, Express. js, Node. js
- Database Management: MongoDB
- Version Control: GitHub, GitLab
- Soft Skills: Communication, Team Building, Report Writing

Work Experience

Umpteen Financial Services

Cashier

October 2023 - Present

- Recorded daily cash inflows and outflows
- Updated accounts receivable and accounts payable and performed reconciliations
- Made reminder calls to clients about repayment dates

Watoto Child Care Ministries

Internship

June 2023 - August 2023

- Conducted residential psychosocial support visits to improve the wellbeing of mothers and children
- Trained and sensitized new foster mothers about child welfare processes
- Conducted field visits to courts following child protection commitment recommendations
- Handled indiscipline cases during home department visits
- Worked on care plans for children under the ministry

Education

Refactory Academy

Certificate in Software Engineering with JavaScript

February 2024 - May 2024

Africa Renewal University, Uganda

Diploma in Social Work and Social Administration 2020 - 2023

St Gerald's Senior Secondary School, Uganda

Advanced Certificate of Education 2018 - 2019 Referees

Mr. Vicent Byamukama Vice Chancellor Africa Renewal University Tel: 0782-445439

Nyakato Irene Facilitator Refactory Academy Tel: 0752933257

Tugumy Andrew Facilitator Refactory Academy Tel: 0755017384